Yes, we get superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep within your dreams.
Taking aim for your
heart so it would seem.
Stand tall and read, go to
hell and jump for paradise.
Every time dangerous, dangerous.
We like it serious, serious, oh.
Looking deep in the dream,
there is the one in pain.
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today.
Adventure calls now, let's go.
The balls built between
us, they will show.
Still what we don't know.
Yes, working hard together.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream.
Despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through.
Believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
All the love and the tears.
In the world we're in.
United gently bringing up.
Our thought again, yeah.
We're the foolish ones we love.
We'll carry on till we see the light.
The sun will rise.
The greatest fight at its core.
Is against myself forevermore.
Come on, let's do it now, let's go.
The balls filled between
us, they will show.
So what we don't know.
That's what we call adventure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Superpowers.
Superpowers. Superpowers.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Superpowers.
Yes, with the super powers!
Rain is all motion.
Damn it!
Now we got all strong again!
Now, now, now!
Conkron!
It's Donut!
Power, Mochi!
Oh, decided on a new look?
It's quiet.
One might say too quiet.
Everything's clear.
All clear here.
Big Mom won't allow her
reputation to be tarnished.
This is only a temporary reprieve.
That may be so, but we've made
our choice and we must carry on.
Exactly.
Right now, our priority
is getting back on course.
That's simple enough.
The cake.
It's the only way to pacify Big Mom's
wrath and reunite with our crew.
I don't suspect that this
will go off without a hitch,
but we have to have faith in our friends
and make sure that we don't let them down.
This is a message to
every island in Totoland.
We must prepare for battle.
Dispatch all Dodge ships immediately.
The honor of the Big
Mom Pirates is at stake.
There are three pirate crews
who must face our wrath. First,
the Straw Hats,
who in a short time have caused immeasurable
damage to our home and our pride.
Second are the traitors,
the Fire Tank Pirates.
They repaid Mama's generosity with deceit,
plotting to assassinate her and
destroying Pudding's wedding.
And finally the Sun Pirates, the
two-faced associates of Jinbe.
He declared an open revolt against
Mama, and his crew turned tail and ran.
But all three of those detestable crews
are still within the seas of Totoland,
fleeing to save their lonely lives.
So we're supposed to search for them?
What happened to the Territory Slugs?
I don't know the story, but it
sounds like they all disappear.
What?
Show no mercy.
Don't let a single enemy
leave our territory.
Put them down like the
filthy animals they are.
Steal the bastards limb from limb.
Fury their ships at the bottom of the sea.
Yeah!
I think it's clear now.
As long as I keep my cool, you
have no hope of defeating me.
I can make you drop your guard again.
You are not invincible.
I'll show you.
It seems like you're shrinking.
Oh crap, guess I'm done
using fourth gear for now.
Okay then, time out.
Thanks for giving me a heads up.
Right, I gotta get far away.
Hold out for ten minutes,
then I can use Haki.
So his power-up has a time limit.
I'm not so generous as to let you escape.
I need those ten minutes.
I'm gonna get wrecked
if I don't have my Haki.
Damn it! He's catching up!
This is bad!
It's really, really bad!
Overall weapon.
I'm almost disappointed.
What do I do?
Huh?
What the heck happened to him?
Hey, you okay?
You're not dead, right?
It happened when he
tried the whipped cream.
No, it can't be.
Do you think it was poisoned? What?
Just ask him if he liked it.
I could die happy because it's so tasty.
The cream almost took him to heaven.
Why, it's dangerously delicious.
That whipped cream is
the secret ingredient.
He was talking about the
essence of true sweetness.
This is it—the ultimate cream!
It's called Simpson whip.
I'm sorry, pudding, but there's
no way I can allow that.
We can't afford to lose you.
I could never do this without your help.
help
The whole point is to not pass out.
To think if such exquisite
cream was spread on a cake.
Your imagination's going to kill you.
And here you have my
famous fluffy chiffon cake.
What do you think?
Oh yeah, hold it down. Hurry!
It's so fluffy that it's gonna float away.
I just finished up my work.
As well, it's perfectly
smooth and perfectly sweet.
The freshest and finest chocolate with
a hint of Sanji's whipped cream too.
We gotta put a lid on it
because this chocolate's
so smooth it's slipping
right out of the pot.
Five
minutes till
six—everything's right on schedule.
Is
the ship ready?
Yes, sir! It is.
To save some time, we'll put the finishing
touches on the cake after we set sail.
The Sunny is on its way here, and
I want to meet up with it asap.
Yes, sir!
sir You got it.
I'm ready to go.
Well, all right, then.
Let's finish up this cake
and go take down an emperor.
Why are you in disguise, sir?
I'm shy.
Clear the way for us, everyone.
We need to take the cake to the port.
That's awesome.
They threw it together so fast.
They're really gonna pull this off.
Wow, it smells so good.
Mama will surety love
this cake when it's done.
I don't even need to taste it.
The smell is good enough.
Or, or...
I'd expect nothing less from
Lady Pudding and Lady Chiffon.
Don't forget WCI-31.
can't leave mama waiting
can we wouldn't dream of it
you just wait big mom this
cake is gonna blow your mind
Power march in!
Is that Pulmei?
Katakuri!
Help before he captures me!
Help me!
Where are you going?
Hey, come back!
Dammit!
Barrel!
That was close.
Where are we? A house?
You're okay, Branch. Thanks.
My name is Barrel!
Got it.
Well, thank you, Branch.
What did I just say?
I can relax in here
while I get my Haki back.
You are a monster!
What the heck?
Give me my cake!
Please, stop!
This isn't cake!
Mama, listen to me.
You've come to the wrong
place. She's right.
There's no wedding king here.
Just lots of nuts.
Straw Hat is elsewhere.
Straw Hat, where are you?
That's big mom.
Whoa!
That must be Chiffon!
Who else could it be?
My sweet little girl!
Oh, grown-up!
Not so fast, Pudding!
Damn.
I'm sorry, Oven. Can this wait?
Depends.
Where do you intend to
take that wedding cake?
I understand that you want
to stop Mama's hunger bangs,
but the plan was to ambush
her and the Straw Hats here.
We decided to finish the cake on
a ship and intercept Mama at sea.
Why the hell at sea?
Because it ensures that Mama won't
cause any damage to Chocolat Town.
All we have to do is give Press a call,
then we can all meet up and stop her.
I.
Agree, that is a splendid plan!
Pardon me then please
carry on and good luck.
Thank you oven.
I promise we won't let you down.
I don't mean you
You're staying here with me stop it
No, how could he do that to his sister?
Why would you do such a thing, sir?
This matter is none of your concern.
It's a family issue.
Hey, let them carry the cake to the porch.
Sir!
Chiffon, no!
We're in trouble.
How dare you?
After what happened, you should know better
than to show your face in front of me.
You share a part in your
husband's unforgivable crime?
Did you think I would simply forget?
Even if you were family,
treason's a heavy sin.
Let her go!
She came here to help!
Pudding, wait!
If you get in his way, he'll
brand you a traitor too.
He's worried about me!
But if I blow my cover to save
her, we could all be screwed.
What should I do?
I...
I didn't come back to give up.
My debt to Nami won't be repaid
until they leave here safely.
Big brother!
I can't die till that cake is done!
Let me help them!
they saved loneless life i can't
die i have to fight to the end
you're not some teenager going
through a rebellious phase wake up
you're a traitor who tried to
assassinate the leader of our country
it brings me no joy to kill
my little sister like this
Then please stop it We need to set an
example for other would-be traitors We have
to help her I don't have time to worry
about the consequences But I need an opening
Get your hands off her right
now Armin, do you hear me?
He'll save you, sweetie.
Hold on! Huh? Who's that guy?
You again?
I thought I'd toss your
dumb ass into the sea!
Thanks, whoever you are.
Now I just have to get her to safety
before anyone notices I was here.
Time to fly, Shafana. Huh?
Time to fly, Shafana.
I just knocked over Minister Oven.
Who is Oven and where did he come from?
Yes, I'm pretty strong.
I had no idea.
Huh?
That obviously wasn't you, dammit!
I'm not at war!
Question is, who was it?
You saved me.
Sorry I kept you waiting for so long.
No, it's fine.
Here, Chiffon, head under this.
Let's hurry to the shore.
More, more!
Clear the way, everyone!
Blackleg rescued me, but...
Hold on...
Who in the world was that guy?
It's odd!
Ah!
There.
Oven!
Clever hiding place.
That's enough, Oven! Stop it! Rat!
We need her, brother.
If we don't have Shipvon's help,
we can't finish Mama's wedding day.
cake just accept your punishment.
I will burn you until nothing remains!
What is it?
Oven, we found Petchy's ship.
It's heading your way now,
straight to Kaku Island.
Our fleet is pursuing them as we speak.
We'll drive them into the port.
It can't be.
Petchy, why?
And here I thought your husband
was going to leave you to die.
I guess he's not as heartless as he seems.
Petchy.
Hey, Benji!
It's me, Auburn.
Wait, Auburn's there?
I just caught your accomplice,
or rather your dear wife, as she was
about to leave Kaku Island. What?
Little.
Have they captured the madam?
Conveniently, we just left town
and are heading to the port now.
So you just keep sailing straight like you
are already and you can
surrender when you can.
Looks like I've been stopped
them before they can take off.
They expected trouble,
but this is a damn mess.
She may be my sister, but I
will kill her on the spot.
So I make extra sure you
don't step out of line.
Benji, just ignore him.
Turn around and run away.
I'm the one who decided to
come here in the first place.
If they capture you, they're
still going to execute all of us.
Even if I die, I want you to live.
Mama has hated me for years.
You guys are my real family.
You showed me the meaning of love.
So live on, and someday,
take revenge for me!
As if we could just
leave you and go, Lili!
Stop talking nonsense!
Shafan, no!
Fine, Oven.
We'll enter the port like you said.
Hands up, no funny business!
You got my boy, but you keep
your dirty little mitts off.
As your fun capisce
very well then,
who knew you were such a softy?
This is gonna cost you your neck!
You really should have run away.
Banshee's ship is pulling in!
All soldiers, prepare to fire on command!
Tarts, separate into right and left
flanks and block their escape route!
Sir!
Well, I'll be damned, there he is.
That was easy.
So he's surrendering
without a fight after all.
Minister Evans' carriage
is arriving at the port.
It's Straw Hat!
What the hell? And Barrel.
Help me, Amand, please!
Huh?
Is that guy over there Straw Hat?
What is he doing here?
Mama!
You see that?
It seems Straw Hat showed up after all!
And he must have my case!
He thought Big Mom was chasing the Sunny!
What gives, Bridge?
Did this situation make any sense to you?
Please rescue me, Mama!
Mama!
Oh, crap!
She's after me!
Well, star hat, where
are you hiding my cake?
I don't know, but it's not here!
Mama, Press, anyone help?
Release my sister!
Dandy Wolf!
Right, it's time for third gear!
All right, Kum Kum!
Giant pistol!
No use, I can't break it without my Haki!
There's no escape.
It's surrounding us!
Slow walks.
Yikes!
I know you're trying to help,
but please don't cut me too!
My famed Blade Shit longs to deliver
a painful, lingering death to you.
I hate to run, but I can't
fight you guys right now!
No!
Gotta find a mirror! Quick!
This is a problem, Pedos.
Your wall is in my way.
Candy Slug!
Give me my cake!
I just have to keep running
till I get my Haki back!
Give me my cake!
I'll help!
Heros, please stop her.
This is my city.
I know you want to kill Straw
Hat, but focus your destruction!
You can't escape, Straw Hat!
Do you hear me?
Damn it!
The whole town is reduced to rubble!
Where is Straw Hat?
He's gone.
Man, was that close or what?
Hold on.
Maybe it's good that Big Mom is here.
Not good for me so much, but it means
the others must have gotten away safely.
Ships!
I see the enemy!
The Big Mom Pirates are catching up!
Understood. You ready? Yes.
All this running around was getting dull.
I say we fight. Yeah!
Leave it to us!
Let's do this, Carrot!
Are you there?
Hello?
Carrot!
Hey!
We got a big battle coming, so get ready!
The sky.
Look.
Huh?
Is tonight gonna be a full moon?
Mr. Ruppet!
Those idiots.
That was smooth as hell, father!
Remember this, Pez. Watch close.
This is how I roll.
It's your papa's way of life. Yes!
Nice work, Veggie.
Whatever you do next, we've got your back.
Straw Hat is here.
Someone please help me!
Would you shut up, Branch? It's Barrel.
This is Chip's Town.
Straw Hat Luffy has been
sighted in this area.
Let me go.
This is Chock Full Town.
Straw Hat has been sighted. What?
He was just in Chip's Town.
He's popping up all over the place.
He must be running through the Miro World.
Oh, come on, Barrel.
Did you really get caught again?
This is Greentown!
We have multiple calls from citizens
reporting that they saw someone suspicious!
It could be Straw Hat!
What are you trying to pull here?
If you want to escape, then
just go to Cacao Island. Huh?
How do you know about our plan?
I was eavesdropping on you.
Now everybody knows.
Are you kidding me?
Just give it up.
There's no way you'll
ever defeat my brother.
Haki doesn't last forever.
If the fight goes on long enough, his
observation powers will get weaker.
I'm sure of it.
Wee, wee, wee, wee.
You look like a dope, but you're
pretty sharp when it comes to fighting.
I still need something more.
Luffy,
I gave you the best lessons I could,
but Haki becomes much stronger
in the heat of battle.
That will be the true test.
And the stronger the enemies you face,
the faster your own strength will evolve.
I wonder if I could see the future.
Even just a little.
What are you talking about?
Don't push your luck, you little shrimp.
I want to surpass him.
I want to fight him at his full strength,
and then I'll defeat him,
the Billionberry Man.